patriotmemory.com 2013-12-06

# 

To be the vendor of choice for the computer and consumer electronic industries with a commitment to service and quality. Commitment, focus on innovation in technology, product quality, and customer satisfaction are the key enablers of our future success. Established in 1985, Patriot Memory builds a full range of memory module and flash memory products, offering a perfect blend of quality and value. Patriot products include Extreme Performance (EP), Signature Lines (SL) and Flash Memory solutions (FM). 

47027 Benicia Street  
Fremont, CA 94538  
Phone: (510) 979-1021  
Fax: (510) 979-1564.

Patriot has sales offices located throughout the U.S. and Asia.  Patriot sells through the distribution channels throughout North America, Europe, Asia Pacific, Middle East, Africa, and Latin America. 

We understand the value of designing and responding quickly and intelligently to the rapid changes inherent in the memory module industry.  This commitment to R&D enables us to deliver the best quality memory modules powered by the latest innovative technology. 

To meet the growing global demand for its products, Patriot manufactures its Extreme Performance (EP), Dual Channel (DC) and Signature Line (SL) products in it own state-of-the-art manufacturing facility with highly skilled staff in Fremont, California USA and Taipei, Taiwan.

Patriot is a member of JEDEC.  You can feel confident that your Patriot modules are of the highest quality available. 

Patriot's development and manufacturing facility are located in Fremont, California USA and Taipei, Taiwan.  Our manufacturing segment is composed of a highly skilled production staff and multiple production lines optimized for modules, giving Patriot the ability and resources necessary to provide a full line of memory module solutions. 

Patriot Memory ensures that every module meets or exceeds industry standards.  The manufacturing process begins with high-quality components and ends with rigorous functional testing to ensure each module's reliability and compatibility.

Patriot Memory modules are approved by leading motherboard and system manufacturers such Intel, Tyan, Supermicro and Iwill. Patriot Memory is a member of Apple Developer Connection. Awards from such leading product review sites as XBit Labs, Anandtech, Tom's Hardware and Hot Hardware.com demonstrate Patriot EP and DC+XBLK memory modules set the standard for performance and reliability.

Patriot's goal is to be your memory solutions provider with high quality products and services that are value priced. With our courteous and knowledgeable sales and technical support staff, industry leading warranty terms, and customizable logistic services; we feel there is no requirement we can not satisfy.

For customer support information, please click on Contact Us. 

Patriot Memory  
47027 Benicia Street  
Fremont, CA 94538  

Local:510-979-1021  
TOLL FREE800-800-9600  
Fax:510-979-1586  

Patriot Memory B.V.  
Innsbruckweg 190-192  
3047 AH Rotterdam  
The Netherlands  

Local:+31 (0)10 2931 250  
Fax:+31 (0)10 2931 251  

**Patriot Memory  
11F, No. 700, Jhong Jheng Road  
Jhong He District, New Taipei City, 23552  
Taiwan, R.O.C.**  

Local:+886 2 8228 0333 ext. 101  
Fax: **+886 2 8228 0339**   

Thank you for your interest in Patriot Memory! We are excited that you are interested in our company.

To submit your resume, e-mail your resume as an attachment or formatted as ASCII to [careers@patriotmem.com](mailto:careers@patriotmem.com).If you are interested in a specific position listed, please include the Job Title and/or Job Code found on the job posting in your e-mail.

If you have any questions regarding employment with Patriot Memory, please e-mail [careers@patriotmem.com](mailto:careers@patriotmem.com).

Patriot Memory is an equal opportunity employer.

  * Regional Sales Manager, Russia

**Job Summary:  **

Regional Sales Manager maintains and expands relationships with strategically important large customers. Initially assigned to three to five named customers, the Regional Sales Manager is responsible for increasing sales revenue quarter over quarter. The Regional Sales Manager reports to the VP Sales for the company.

**Specific Job Responsibilities:**   

-Establish productive, professional relationships with key personnel in assigned customer accounts -Meet assigned targets for profitable sales volume and strategic objectives in assigned accounts

-Co-ordinate local Marketing activities tied to the sales goals for the region

-Develop brand presence in channel retail stores: produce and distribute POS, dealers' in-store promotions

-Provide critical thinking to derive maximum sales from customers’ accounts

-Provide competitive analysis for market pricing and internal cost analysis for the designated account

-Develop and execute a sales and marketing plan with goals for each customer account with clear understanding of TAM by product line

-Build run rates and monitor stock levels closely within all accounts to ensure maximum sales potential

-Be able to measure performance accurately weekly / monthly / quarterly

-Run promotions when and where required

-Provide adequate training to resellers on new products

**Requirements:**

-Higher education

-Fluent English, native Russian -5+ years in sales role, developing and maintaining customer accounts

-Good skills in people management and coordination tasks

-Experience in B2B sales

-Thorough knowledge of the local business market/relevant channel -Sales/Customer focus

-Strong commercial awareness and aptitude

-Willingness to travel local within the region

-Excellent leadership/people management abilities

-Interpersonal communication skills / ability to manage and work in a team

-Ability to work from a home office and be self-motivated and driven

**Specific Task and Activities:**

-Develop a Customer Profile on all major customers

      -Customer Name, Address, Corp Revenue, Size

      -Key Management – names, email addresses and contact #s

      -Sales Revenue with Patriot - YOY by month with growth %

      -Product line segmentation – TAM, top 3 competitors, market

-Daily calls with all major customer accounts

      -Manage inventory and sell through on all products

      -Develop and Monitor Promotions for coming week/month – aligning inventory and orders

      -Competitive pricing and product discussion

-Weekly one-on-one meeting with direct manager going over the following items:

       -Sales Revenue versus Plan by product line

       -Sales out report analysis on each major product line

            -Top runners – sales out, inventory, Weeks On Hand (WOH), pricing competitiveness, exposure/promotions

       -Promotional Calendar

            -Work with Product Marketing Managers to define the promotions for the following month with all major accounts

            -Must be completed in a timely fashion per the requirements of the sales channel - lead time of retail to execute MIRs or ad vehicles

**Compensation:**

This is a commissioned position, with commission structure based on revenue results, and a supporting base salary.

Patriot Memory LLC is an Equal Opportunity Employer

Patriot's FUEL+ Mobile Rechargeable Battery to power re-charging station at O.co Coliseum for Oakland A's fans in need of charge

Fremont, California, USA, August 20, 2013 – Patriot Memory, a global pioneer in high-performance memory, NAND flash, storage, accessories and enthusiast computer products today announces a new marketing partnership with the Oakland Athletics. As smartphones and tablets have become an essential part of everyday life—as well as fan favorites for checking sports stats and fantasy teams at the ball field—keeping devices powered up has become more and more of a challenge. For A's fans looking to power up their favorite mobile devices to stay on top of their game, Patriot will feature their new faster charging 2.5A FUEL+ mobile rechargeable batteries at a charging station at the O.co Coliseum during select games during the remainder of the season. Provided as a free service, fans are invited to come plug in at the charging station to grab some extra juice for their mobile phone or tablet using Patriot’s FUEL+ batteries. In addition, Patriot will be providing FUEL+ units for guests on the A's pre- and post-game radio shows to fuel up everyone’s favorite Oakland A's sports players and personalities.

"We're thrilled to be partnering with the Oakland A's and to be providing a service to their great fans," said JR Wakabayashi, Global Marketing Manager for Patriot.  "The Fuel+ offers the perfect solution for people on the go in need of power and we can’t think of a better place to demonstrate the speed, portability, ease of use and performance of the FUEL + than at the ballgame when you need and want it most."

"The A's are committed to providing the best possible in-stadium experience for our fans, and this partnership is another example of that commitment," said Ken Pries, vice president of communications and broadcasting for the A's. "We understand our fans' desire to stay connected, and the FUEL + will ensure our fans maintain those connections without missing any of the action on the field."

About FUEL +

Take it, Charge it, Fuel Up. Perfect for anyone on-the-go, Patriot’s FUEL+ mobile rechargeable batteries are the best and most reliable solutions to ensure you will always have power for your mobile devices when you need it. Ranging in size from 1500mAh up-to 9000mAh, The FUEL+ product family features a full line of battery sizes to fit the needs of any mobile user. To safeguard against under-discharge, over-charge, and short-circuit, FUEL+ comes with built-in protection to ensure efficient and safe charging cycles. The FUEL+ also features power pass through technology that enables the battery to be charged when plugged in to a USB or wall outlet, while charging devices. Always have peace of mind when you are mobile, stay charged with FUEL+.

  **FREMONT, CALIF., USA – September 12th, 2013 -**  Patriot, a global pioneer in high-performance memory, NAND flash, storage, and mobile accessories today launches the new high capacity Supersonic Boost XT 256GB USB 3.0 performance drive. 

Offering the enhanced transfer speed of up-to 150MB/s, the Supersonic Boost XT 256GB drive provides excellent performance; making it the perfect solution for those who rely on having fast access to their data and media while trying to manage a busy lifestyle. This high capacity Supersonic Boost XT features the same award winning ultra-durable rubberized housing the Supersonic Boost XT line has been known. This housing provides best in class protection for worry free use even in the most rugged applications.

"Our Supersonic Boost XT product family provides some of the most rugged and best performing drives on the market", says Meng Jay Choo, Patriot's USB Product Manager. “Now with a 256GB capacity, this line will offer one of the largest flash drive capacities as well, at a very reasonable price point.

• Hi Speed USB 3.0 Compatible (backwards compatible to USB 2.0)

• 256GB: Up to 150MB/sec Read; Up to 30MB/sec Write

• Easy plug-and-play functionality

• The rubberized housing provides a durable and rugged exterior that safeguards the drives from the elements. It is protected from any shock and physical damage as well as water resistant offering protection from various elements.

• Compatible with Windows® 8, Windows® 7, Windows Vista®, Windows XP®, Windows 2000®, Windows® ME, Linux 2.4 and later, Mac® OS9, X and later.

About Patriot

Patriot designs, manufactures and markets high performance, enthusiast memory modules, flash memory, and mobile accessory products. Patriot products have become world renown for their extreme performance, reliability and innovation. Patriot sells its products through original equipment manufacturers, retailers, e-tailers and distributors throughout the world with operations in North America, Asia and Europe. Patriot Memory LLC was founded in 1985 and is headquartered in Fremont, California, USA.

All company and/or product names may be trade names, trademarks and/or registered trademarks of the respective owners with which they are associated. Features, pricing, availability, and specifications are subject to change without notice. All company and/or product names may be trade names, trademarks and/or registered trademarks of the respective owners with which they are associated. Features, pricing, availability, and specifications are subject to change without notice.

Environmental conservation has always been at the forefront of Patriot Memory's intrinsic values, and we pride ourselves in our commitment to reduce our carbon footprint. Being recognized as a Bay Area Green Business further validates that the green initiatives we've implemented are accomplishing that goal.

Some of the initiatives we have undertaken are in the areas of energy and water conservation, waste reduction through participation in recycling programs, and reduction of raw material consumption by creating smaller packaging for our products.

Patriot is also is fully compliant with all EPA standards, HAZMAT codes, and we participate in the Spare the Air Program. We are constantly looking into different ways to ensure that Patriot Memory is a greener company. 

| 

## What is the Green Business Program?

The Green Business Program is a successful partnership of environmental agencies and utilities that assists, recognizes and promotes businesses and government agencies that volunteer to operate in a more environmentally responsible way. To be certified "green," participants must be in compliance with all regulations and meet program standards for conserving resources, preventing pollution and minimizing waste. We offer motivated businesses and agencies an easy-to-use framework for improving environmental performance. Over 1500 businesses and public agencies have been certified since 1996 bay area wide and over 330 of those are in Santa Clara County.

For more information about this program, please visit http://www.greenbiz.ca.gov/  
  
---|---  
| 

## What is Spare the Air Program?

The Spare the Air Program was established by the The Bay Area Air Quality Management District in 1991 to reduce air pollution and provide advance notice when a "Spare the Air Alert" is in effect. The Air District declares Spare the Air Alerts on days when air quality is forecast to exceed federal standards.

For more information about this program, please visit http://sparetheair.org/   
  
Patriot Memory understands the value of information and has a respect for your privacy. We are pleased to provide this Privacy Statement to inform you of our practices concerning the collection and use of information about visitors to Patriot web site.

## Personal Information

In general, you can visit Patriot Memory on the Internet without telling us who you are and without giving any personal information about yourself. You may choose to provide us with personal information in a variety of situations. For example, you may want to provide us with information, such as your name and address or e-mail address, to send us e-mail, process an order or rebate, submit a request for technical support, participating in an online survey, or register for a service. The information is collected only to help us serve you, and help us better understand your needs and interests. Personal data collected online may also be combined with information you provide Patriot through other sources such as trade shows or conferences.

Patriot Memory does not collect or maintain information from anyone know to be under the age of 13 and we maintain COPPA disclosure in our User Agreement.

Patriot Memory does not and will not collect or maintain information about you, your activities on this site or in the forums, or track your browsing activities. Patriot Memory will never send you spam or email solicitations, any other unsolicited commercial or advertising communications.

Certain information must be transferred between our server and visitors' computers for this site to function and display properly. The following information is obtained by our server and logged:

Your IP (Internet Protocol) address  
Where you came from  
What pages you visited  
The operating system and browser you are using  
If you downloaded any files  

This non-personal information is utilized solely to provide us with valuable data about the amount of traffic to and from our website. It may help determine what is popular on the website and what is not, and to see where and how people find information on our website.

You will not find any malicious code, scripts, web-bugs, spyware programs or applications on our website. We use various scripts for maintaining news feeds, providing features and visitor conveniences, site security, and in our forums. None are malicious and/or inherently or realistically dangerous in any way.

From time to time, we may provide software downloads, scripts, documents, or materials for the convenience of our members and visitors.

If the content of our website is illegal in your country and/or territory, the use of this site is strictly prohibited.

Patriot Memory prohibits the posting of working direct links or any other items which would result in prohibited items being downloaded to a user's computer. It violates the User Agreement each registered member must agree as part of the registration process.

At no time will this site ever attempt to place, or allow to be placed, any "tracking" or "data mining" cookie or similar file on any member or visitor's computer.

Patriot Memory hates Spam! We hate spammers worse!! Anyone who harvests, or attempts to, member or visitor information for the purpose of spamming or otherwise sending unsolicitted email is strictly prohibited and will not be tolerated.

Patriot Memory has implemented and maintained methods to prevent information about you from being harvested from this site. Any and all legal remedies available will be used to prosecute offenders.

The following Forum information is obtained and maintained for the proper administration of registered memberships and the forums. Patriot Memory will not use or share the information you provide with any third parties except as otherwise provided for in this Privacy Policy. 

If you choose to register at the forums your user name is maintained If you post any message to a forum your IP address and the message you posted is maintained If you provide additional information in your Profile after registering

You can access all the personally identifiable information we collect and maintain except your IP address for modifications by editing your user profile. IP address info cannot be changed as this data is automatically logged by the Forum's software and cannot be edited.

In no way will Patriot Memory change your personal information. You are the only one to whom the data belongs and we take it very serious to keep your information private!

Patriot Memory reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time. In the event the Privacy Policy is amended, updated or materially changed, we will give notice of this fact in a manner which is easily accessible and clearly apparent to both visitors and members. We will implement our Privacy Policy in such a way so as to never compromise your trust or your privacy. However, we must reserve the right to make changes which address issues that may arise in the future.

For questions or concerns please send an email to (list an e-mail address you want) 

©1985-2012 Patriot Memory® LLC. All Rights Reserved. .

Loading...
